digiex.net 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy | Digiex

Last modified: 30th December 2016 **Data Collection:**

**Guest:**  
We collect no information ourselves on you. However as our site uses Google Analytics, Google Ads and Facebook Connect your viewing history may be collected by them.   
To stop this you can enable the '[Do Not Track](http://donottrack.us/)' signal in your browser, disable third party cookies or use browser extensions to block tracking.

**Members:**  
Same as above for guests, plus also when registering as a member of Digiex, we collect your Email Address, Username and Password (and any other optional details you give us).

 **Data Storage:**

Members details are stored in a database on the server, as well as on offsite backups. Offsite backups are encrypted and only stored for a small period of time as needed.  
Passwords are not stored as plaintext, they are hashed and salted for security so that in the event of a data breach they are unusable.

 **Data Usage:**

We use your information solely for use on this website to allow you to login and post.   
We have no commercial interest in your personal data.

 **Cookies:**

We use a number of different cookies on our site. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance.

The list below describe the cookies we use on this site and what we use them for. Currently we operate an ‘implied consent’ policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete the cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called "Incognito" in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, "Private Browsing" in Firefox and Safari etc.)

**Google Analytics** : We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behaviour on our website. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information. We therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.

You can find out more about Google's position on privacy as regards its analytics service at [http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html](https://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html)

**XenForo** : Our websites runs the popular XenForo CMS and forum and cookies are used to store basic data on your interactions with XenForo, and whether you have logged into XenForo. We use a session cookie to remember your log-in for you if you are a registered user and we deem these as being strictly necessary to the working of the website. If these are disabled then various functionality on the site will be broken.

More information on session cookies and what they are used for at <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/session-cookies-used-for.html>

**Third Party Cookies:** These are cookies set on your machine by external websites whose services are used on this site. Cookies of this type are the sharing buttons across the site allow visitors to share content onto social networks. Cookies are currently set by Facebook. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of our website. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the internet, including on this website.

You should check the respective policies of each of these sites to see how exactly they use your information and to find out how to opt out, or delete, such information.

 **Ad Serving:**

Third party vendors, including Google, Infolinks and Skimlinks, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits.

Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to sites on the Internet.  
You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

Skimlinks use of Cookie's can be viewed [here](http://skimlinks.com/privacy-policy#users) and can be opted out at: <http://skimlinks.com/opt-out>

That concludes the Digiex Privacy Policy.
